Evan Garrett

North Carolina, USA 912-312-2193 evang522@gmail.com

Full Stack Web Developer

github.com/evang522 linkedin.com/in/evang522 evanhgarrett.com

-PROFILE-

I am a Full stack Javascript Developer with experience in the workflow of developing Node.js/React/MongoDB-PostgresQL applications on a team. I have fully developed or contributed to more than 5 applications running in production, and honed skills to troubleshoot issues and add new features to any part of the Javascript Stack.

-WHERE I EXCEL-

DatabaseMongoDB, Mongoose.js, PostgresQL, Knex.jsApplication LogicNode.js, Express.js, Socket.io, JWT AuthenticationFrontendReact.js, Redux, jQuery, HTML5, CSS3CI & DeployTravis CI, Netlify, AWS, HerokuWorkflowGit, npm, yarn, Github, Bitbucket

-EXPERIENCE-

Desktop Engineer, Athens Micro, Athens, Georgia—November 2015-October 2017

Played a considerable tech role in a growing business IT company, supporting over 300 businesses in the Southeast United States, onsite and remotely managing and troubleshooting business computer networks, network technology, and performing business disaster recovery ops. Individually responsible for leading proactive and responsive tech support for a number of the company's specific clients.

Student Technician, Toccoa Falls College; Toccoa Falls, Georgia — May 2013- May 2014

Maintained Staff, Faculty, and Library Computer Technology. Contributed to College Research regarding Library and Staff technology integration.

Student Technician, Armstrong Atlantic State University; Savannah, Georgia — 2009-2010

Maintained Computer Lab, Staff, and Faculty computer hardware and software.

-SIDE PROJECTS-

Drystore <u>https://github.com/evang522/drystore</u>

- Dried food storage and analytics platform for organizing sustenance in emergency situations.

- Service connecting organizations in need of web work with tech volunteers.

Platform for storing, accessing, and playing back MP3 Links, written in Python.

-EDUCATION-

Thinkful Engineering Immersion, November 2017: Full Stack Javascript Bootcamp

- 6 month intensive education in best-practice workflow developing Full-Stack MongoDB/PostgresQL, Express.js, React, Redux, Node applications.
- Data Science and Algorithms course focusing computer science, algorithm runtime complexity, and efficiency in data processing.

Toccoa Falls College, May 2014: Bachelor of Science, Philosophy, Cum laude

- Focus on Analytic Philosophy, Philosophy of Religion, Metaphysics, Politics, and Ethics.